好了，选一张卡 好
Pick a card.Okay
记住花色号码
All right. Now,memorize it.
好了没？ 好了
-You got it? -Oh,yes.
是这张吗？
Is that your card?
就是这张
Yes.
大家好
-Hey,guys. -Hi there!
你们猜怎么着？ 班要上电视拍广告了
Guess what. Ben is gonna be in a TV commercial.
你们在说什么？
What are you talking about?
还没有定案
It's not for sure,but...
不过我们在公园里遇到一个人 他觉得班很可爱
...we met this guy in the park who thought Ben was cute.
这也是事实啦
You know,which he is.
所以那个人留了张名片 要我带班去参加广告试镜
He gave us his card...and told us to bring him for this commercial he's auditioning.
这个人是本地最大的选角导演
This guy's the biggest commercial casting director in town!
班去公园随便散个步 就有试镜自动送上门！
Ben takes one lousy walk in the park and gets an audition?
我是说，班，真有你的
I mean,way to go,Ben!
那个公园我都去了几百万次了 从来没人主动找我去试镜
I've been in that park a million times and no one's offered me an audition.
我知道，真的很神奇 我们只是在陪班玩荡秋千…
It's crazy. We were pushing Ben on the swings
我每次都在玩荡秋千啊
I'm always on the swings!
我是哪里做错了？
What am I doing wrong?
荡秋千
That.
本集播出：“瑞秋吸烟”
The One Where Rachel Smokes
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
我要出门了，祝我好运
-Gotta go. Wish me luck. -Good luck.
瑞秋，既然你在罗夫罗兰工作 能不能带几件衬衫回来？
Since you work at Ralph Lauren,can you get me some shirts?
第一天上班就偷公司东西 我可能下不了手喔
I don't know if I'd feel comfortable stealing on my very first day.
不愿意从公司偷窃
Unwilling to steal from work.
有意思
Interesting.
就算有人能拿免费的 那也非我莫属
If anybody gets free stuff,it's me.
好了，各位，祝我好运吧
Okay,guys,way to wish me luck.
祝你好运，给他们好看
Go get 'em!
好，来讨论帮瑞秋庆生的事
Let's discuss Rachel's birthday.
我建议在周末办惊喜派对
I say we throw a surprise party this weekend.
可是一个月后才是她生日啊
But her birthday's not for another month.
是没错，但在生日当天开派对 那就不惊喜啦
If we throw her party on her birthday,it's not a surprise.
我觉得这主意不错
Great!
我们办个晚餐派对 邀请好朋友过来
We can have a dinner party and just invite her close friends.
罗斯！
Ross!
我们要帮瑞秋办惊喜派对
We're having a surprise party for Rachel.
好！
Okay
搞定
Done.
好，那你要一起来吗？ 乐意之至
Great. Wanna do it together?I'd love to do it together!
她们要一起来耶
They're gonna do it together.
兄弟，那位可是我女友
That's my girlfriend.
所以我就得闭嘴？
So I gotta shut it down now?
好，我得走了
I gotta go.
我要接班去参加大试镜
I'm picking up Ben...and then we're off to the big audition.
看到有演员假装是班的父亲 那种感觉一定很怪
It's gonna be weird seeing some actor pretending to be Ben's dad.
是啊
Yes
比看班的两个妈妈亲热还要怪吗？
Weirder than seeing his two moms make out?
爸爸？广告里面有爸爸？
Dad? There's a dad in the commercial?
是啊，班和爸爸喝汤 演得很陶醉的样子
Yeah. The dad and Ben eat soup and pretend to enjoy it.
或许我可以跟你们一起去 搞不好能试镜演那个爸爸
Maybe I'll go with you and audition as the dad.
说到扮演班的爸爸 由我这教父上场更最适合了
Who better to play Ben's father than his godfather?
你不是班的教父 什么？
-You're not his godfather. -What?
你在开玩笑吧？
Are you kidding?
当然是啊
Of course I am.
我们走吧，教父 好耶
-Okay,let's go,godfather. -All right!
他们允许我试镜了
They're gonna let me audition!
真的？太棒了 我知道…
Really? That's great!
有个女的看过我演舞台剧 所以我离得她远远的
One of the casting ladies has actually seen me in a play.So I steered clear of her.
另一个我也认识 原因你也知道…
And the other one,I know from....Well,you know.
那个孩子看起来很眼熟
-That kid looks familiar. -Oh,yeah.
是啊，他拍过一堆广告
He's done tons of commercials.
糖果广告、PS游戏机
I've seen him in Sugar Smacks,PlayStation...
还帮电话公司拍过广告
...and that one for the phone company.
他演得实在是太好了 说服我换了电话公司
He was so good,he convinced me to switch phone companies.
钱德因此还气得半死
Chandler was mad.
不过他这次休想拿到这角色 因为班比他可爱多了
He's not gonna get this one. Ben is way cuter than that kid.
看就知道，宝贝，看看你
I mean,look at him.
很好，如果我能演班的爸爸 这样是不是很棒？
That's great.Wouldn't it be great if I got to play Ben's dad?
乔伊，你跟班一点都不像
You look nothing like Ben.
比你像多了
I look more like him than you do.
我跟你还没有熟到生小孩的地步
I really don't know you well enough for you to do that.
现在是最后的二选一
So it's down to these two.
南茜，我知道你喜欢这一个 我也有同感
Nancy,I know you like this one.I think I agree.
瑞秋，你觉得呢？
Rachel,what do you think?
那个是很漂亮
Well,that one is pretty...
但我喜欢这个的面料，抱歉了
...but I just love this fabric.Sorry.
不用抱歉 提供意见是你的职责之一
Don't be. Part of your job is to give your opinions.
功劳归我，开玩笑的
Then I take credit for them. I'm kidding!
她这次是在开玩笑 但下次可别跟她意见相左
She is kidding. But don't ever disagree with her again.
这次换我在开玩笑
Okay,now I'm kidding!
这个办公室真有趣
What a fun office.
我不知道要选哪一个 不过先来根烟倒是真的
I don't know which one. But I do know I need a cigarette.
不如我们出去休息一下 等回来之后再解决？
Let's take a break,go outside and sort this out when we return.
瑞秋？
Rachel？
你抽烟吗？
-You smoke?
不抽，我爸是医生 老跟我说些恐怖的故事…
-No.My dad's a doctor. And he would always tell me horror stories....
说那些鬼神精灵的…
About ghosts and goblins...
完全赞同公主抽烟的权利
...who totally supported the princess' right to smoke.
她们在抽烟的时候 就背着我做出了决定
And then they came back from smoking and they'd made all of the decisions.
这样不太公平 我知道啊！
-That's not fair. -I know.
我不同流合污还被处罚！ 抽烟可是恶心又伤身的习惯
It's like I'm being punished for not having this disgusting,poisonous habit.
对，抽烟最棒了
Yeah,it is the best.
万一这种事没完没了怎么办？
What if this keeps happening?
她们在外头抽烟做决定
They'll be smoking,making the decisions...
我只能在办公室里 呼吸愚蠢的新鲜空气
...and I'll be up in my office breathing in my stupid clean air.
如果金要升我们的职 你们想她会选谁？
And when Kim wants to promote one of us...who do you think she'll pick?
是我还是乌烟瘴气的冒烟女？
... Me or Smokey Smokerson?
我们以前的公司有抽烟区 很棒的喔
We used to have a smoking area at work.
有个小花盆，里头有土 把烟放进去捻熄就行了
It was great. There was this big flowerpot with dirt in it.We used to put our cigarettes out in it.
公司有个元老告诉我 以前里头还有棵小树呢
One of the old-timers told me there used to be a little tree in there.
瑞秋，你也可以一起去 不用抽烟，就说想呼吸点新鲜空气
You can go down there and not smoke. Say you want some fresh air.
对，这是方法
I could do that.
简单点就是一起抽烟
Or you could do the easy thing and smoke.
深深吸它个一口
You gotta take long,deep drags.
我的肺活量还没恢复
Wow,I still don't have my lung capacity back yet.
瑞秋，要去喝咖啡吗？
Rach,do you wanna go get coffee?
乐意之至 好
-I would love to. -Oh,good.
宝贝，我也想一起去
I'm gonna go too.
好啊
Oh,good.
等等，我变卦了
Oh,I changed my mind.
好，来讨论派对的事 我有一大堆点子
Let's talk about the party. I have so many ideas.
我也是
Me too!
哦，这个
Oh,look at that.
好，这是蛋糕的素描图
This is a little sketch of the cake. See?
还有一些菜单的样本
Some sample menus.
不如用意大利风格点心当前菜
I thought we'd start with a Tuscan-style finger food.
至于音乐呢 这是我CD收藏的字母列表
And for music,here's an alphabetized list of all of my CDs.
跟食物超搭配的还做了记号
I've highlighted the ones that'll go with the food.
不是说要亲密的晚餐派对吗？
-What about the intimate dinner party?
现在不那样做了
-We're not doing that.
看来你全包办了，多谢 “共同”主办人
Looks like you took care of everything. Thanks a lot,cohost.
怎么了？我没有一手包办啊 你要做的事还有很多
Wait a minute. There's plenty of things for you to do.
举个例子？
Like what?
杯子
Cups.
杯子？你让我准备杯子？
You're giving me cups?
还有冰块
And ice.
杯子和冰块？ 我可以负责杯子和冰块？
Cups and ice? I get to be in charge of cups and ice?
好吧…
All right.
行，我就来负责杯子和冰块
Fine. I will be in charge of cups and ice.
等等，冰块可以从餐厅拿…
-I can get ice at the restaurant
冰块是我的！…
-I got it!
试镜顺利吗？
-How did the audition go?
不太顺利
-Not so good.
慢着，你在学乔伊那招吗？
Wait a minute. Are you doing Joey's:
“试镜不太顺利”
"The audition didn't go so well....
事实上很顺利！对吧？
Yeah,it did"?
没错！
Yeah,I am!
班取得了第二次试镜的资格
-Yeah,Ben got a second audition. -That's great!
对，我得教罗斯我的戏份 因为我没有过关
I had to teach Ross my bit because I actually didn't get a callback.
你也过关了，对吧？
You got a callback too,didn't you?
没错！
Yeah,I did!
瑞秋，你怎么会来这里？
What are you doing out here?
自己在那里有点无聊 我想来这里呼吸点新鲜空气
It got kind of lonely up there,so I thought I would come out here...and get some fresh air.
南茜和我正好讨论到秋装 太好了
We're discussing the fall collection.Oh,great.
所以这是要…
Anyway,we really
抱歉，瞧你被我们熏的
-Sorry. We're smoking all over you.
不好意思 没关系
-That's okay.
不成…你待着，我们走
We'll move. You stay there.
我把设计寄给罗夫 他很感兴趣
I sent the designs to Ralph. He was excited about it.
太好了，你是最棒的
That's great! You are the best!
不好意思，能给支烟吗？
Excuse me. Can I bum one of those?
这支就好…
Actually,this one's....
你们在聊什么好笑的？
What's so funny over here?
我还以为你不抽烟的
I thought you didn't smoke.
我以为你们是说大麻烟
You know,I thought you guys meant marijuana cigarettes.
像是大麻香烟那种
You know what I mean? Doobies?
我还纳闷你们是疯了不成
Actually,I thought to myself,"Those guys are crazy!"
没啦，我自己也抽烟 天天都抽
But no,I smoke the regular ones all the time.
我们是在抽大麻
We get high.
我也是
Me too.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding.
我也是
Me too.
老天，这真是折磨人 你是怎么习惯的？
Oh,God! This is so nerve-racking. How do you do this?
我过关的经验不多，所以…
Fortunately,I don't get many callbacks,so....
我们在试镜之后被留下来 这是好现象吗？
Is it a good sign that they asked us to wait?
天知道
Who knows?
最后入围的是雷蒙、班 凯尔和乔伊
We have narrowed it down to Raymond,Ben,Kyle...
其余的人，辛苦了，谢谢
...and Joey. The rest of you,thank you.
好耶，我就知道！
Yes! I knew it!
再会
Bye-bye.
后会
So long.
有期
Later.
我不是他老婆喔，他是我前夫 我百分之百是女同志
I'm not married to him anymore. He's my ex-husband. I'm totally gay!
太棒了 我有可能饰演班的爸爸
This is great! I might get to play Ben's dad.
其实那是不可能的
Actually,that can't happen.
因为你们各自的长相都不同
Because you have such different looks...
所以我们把你和雷蒙配对 凯尔和班是一组
...we're putting you with Raymond and Kyle with Ben.
所以最后只有一组会出线
So it'll either be you two or you two.
要命，这样就有点尴尬了 真的是
Man，This is gonna be kind of weird. -Yeah,it is.
对，一定会很尴尬
Yeah. It's gonna be weird.
因为我们是最好的朋友 所以才会尴尬
No. We're like best friends. That's why it's weird.
哦…我以为我们一直在谈话
I thought we were just talking.
如果班拿到广告演出机会 你能帮我弄些免费的汤吗？
If Ben gets this commercial,do you think you can get me some free soup?
钱德，一罐汤才60美分
Chandler,a can of soup is like 60 cents.
对，但是我这五年来 都在供养这29岁的意大利人
Yeah,okay,but I have been supporting a 29-year-old ltalian for five years.
我能把这些东西放这里 等着给瑞秋过生日吗？
Is it okay if I leave this here till Rachel's birthday party?
当然可以，里头是什么？
-Sure. What's in them?
杯子
-Cups.
很好，因为我们替瑞秋 准备了八百加仑的水
Good,because we got Rachel 800 gallons of water.
老实说，这些杯子还真不少
That's a lot of cups.
对，这是因为我负责杯子冰块
I'm in charge of cups and ice.
莫妮卡在这一天将后悔莫及 因为她要我负责杯子冰块
And Monica's gonna rue the day she put me in charge of cups and ice.
我也后悔过一次 除了后悔没做别的
You know,I rued the day once. Didn't get a whole lot else done.
好吧，该把其他杯子搬上来了
Okay,time to bring up the rest of the cups.
乔伊 菲比
Joey  Phoebe
罗斯，你在这里正好 我有事要跟你说
Ross,I'm glad you're here.I want to talk to you.
怎么了？
What's up?
我一直在想这次拍广告的事
I've been thinking about this commercial thing.
我和班对阵，我们俩竞争
Me against Ben.The two of us competing.
这样横竖都不会有好结果
That can't lead to anything good.
我想我还是退出好了 告诉他们我不去试镜
I think I'm just gonna step aside. I'll tell them that I won't audition.
乔伊，太好了，多谢
Joey,that's great. Thanks,man.
就这样？
That's it?
你真要让我这样做？ 这事关我的职业生涯耶
You're gonna let me do this? It's my career we're talking about!
可是你说… 我是要你说出让班退出
But you just…I just said that so you wouldn't let Ben do it.
罗斯，如果真有人要退出 那也应该是班
If anyone should step aside,it should be Ben.
什么？ 钱德，告诉他为什么
-What? -Chandler,tell him!
我先去开门
Well,let me get the door first.
没有人，你好
Hi,no one!
班为什么应该退出？
Why should Ben step aside?
这原本就是他的试镜
It was his audition in the first place.
你是跟过去的 就像是追随者父亲
You tagged along.You're like the tagalong dad!
起码我有顾虑到班的感受
At least I care about his feelings.
什么？
What?
你知道万一他没通过试镜 到时他会有多难过吗？
You know how hard it'll be on him when he doesn't get it?
那他又为什么不会通过？
And why wouldn't he get it?
得了吧？你有没有看过 跟我同组的小子有多厉害？
Come on!Have you seen what my kid can do?
他会拨电话、吃墨西哥脆片
He dials phones,he eats tortilla chips.
还会与卡通老虎踢足球
He plays soccer with the cartoon tiger!
你是说你的小子喝汤 比我儿子厉害？
Are you saying your kid eats soup better than my kid?
你儿子才刚学会喝汤呢
You just give him a spoon,baby.
是吗？我们走着瞧
Oh,yeah? I guess we'll see!
好啊，这支广告片的主角 非我和米契莫属
This commercial belongs to me and Mitch!
你的孩子叫做雷蒙 对，你的也是！
-Your kid's name is Raymond! -Yeah? So is yours!
（中央咖啡馆）
有没有用？
-How did work go?
很棒…我听你们的建议 去她们抽烟的地方
-lt was great.I went down there like you said.
我们讨论到了生意 金完全接受我的意见
And we talked business.And Kim took my opinions.
你浑身烟味
You stink!
多谢
-Thanks.
我是说真的
-No,I'm serious.
因为那里的人全都在抽烟
That's because I went down there and they were smoking.
这其实是成功的味道
This is actually the smell of success.
不过有点怪怪的 天啊，你有抽烟
But there's something different. Oh,my God! You smoked!
我没有
I did not.
才怪，你看起来生病又快乐 你一定有抽烟
Yes,you did. You look happy and sick. You smoked!
好啦…我有抽 为了事业不得已
All right,fine! But I had to. I had to do it for my career.
多么希望我也能为了事业而吸烟
I wish I had to smoke for my career.
这样很恶心耶
But it's so gross!
没那么糟啦
It's not that bad,you know?
虽然舌头有点打结 手指也有点怪味
Yeah,my tongue feels a little fuzzy and my fingers sort of smell.
其实我感觉快吐了
I actually feel like I could throw up.
你知道自己在说什么吗 我知道…我也很后悔
-Can you hear yourself? -I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我脱离了自我，抽了半包烟 感觉怪怪的，还在发抖
I'm not myself. I smoked like half a pack.I feel a little shaky and a little weird.
好，但你一定要撑过这一关 接下来就会是快乐无比了
But you gotta push past this,okay? Because it's about to get so good.
钱德
Chandler
你浑身烟味，我得去透透气
You smell so smoky,I gotta get up.
我没骗你
I'm not kidding.
我觉得你闻起来很香
I think you smell great.
所以大家都同意了 不要格子图案，要粉红？
So we're decided. No on plaid,yes on pink.
完全正确
Absolutely.
我举双手双脚赞成
I'm so onboard.
瑞秋，这支烟不是才刚点？
-Didn't you just light that?
是啊，但是我正在努力少抽烟
-Yeah.But you know what?I'm just really,really trying to cut back,you know.
“瑞秋，祝你好运”
Good luck,Rach.
其实我最近有想要戒烟
I've been thinking about quitting.
那可不，我每周日晚上 都告诉自己要戒烟
Every Sunday night,I tell myself I'm quitting.
结果周一还是狂抽猛抽
Every Monday morning,it's like:
没错
Tell me about it.
那就戒了吧，我们一起戒烟
We'll just quit. Let's all quit!
听起来是很诱人啦
It sounds appealing.
我戒烟从没成功过
-I never could do it.
你可以的，一定行
-But you could. Absolutely.
我们可以互相帮忙
We can help each other.
用那个什么戒烟贴布的 我们能组成戒烟三姐妹
We could get those patches.We could be like the Patch Sisters.
其实我们真的应该戒烟 好吧，一起来戒烟
You know,we really should quit. Okay,let's quit!
好，太棒了，把香烟给我 来，通通交出来
Great! Give me those cigs. Come on!Give it! Out. Done. Quit.
那个打火机是我先夫送我的
My late husband gave me that lighter.
我没在开玩笑
I'm not kidding.
那好吧
Okay,then.
好汤
Mmm...soup.
Mmm…soup
乔伊，罗斯马上就到
Joey，Ross is gonna be here any second
我去上个厕所 帮我看一下班，好吗？
Would you mind watching Ben for me while I use the ladies' room?
好啊，没问题 谢谢
-No problem. -Thanks.
嗨，班
Hi Ben
你想当演员啊？
So you want to be an actor?
告诉你，演戏可不像野餐
I gotta tell you,it's no picnic.
有碰不完的钉子
There's tons of rejection.
一点都不稳定
No stability.
前一天你还是雷莫瑞医生
I mean,one day,you're Dr. Drake Ramoray.
隔天你就要去啃番茄酱
The next day,you're eating ketchup out of the bottle.
这可是艰苦的生活
It's a tough life.
没错啦，你是能决定起床时间
I mean,sure,you can get up whenever you want...
整天看电视也行
...watch TV all day...
在演员训练班里 认识一卡车的女孩
...meet tons of women in acting class....
小子，我干嘛劝你打消念头 这种生活太棒了
Oh,who am I kidding. I can't talk you out of this. It's a great life.
乔伊
-Joey.
罗斯
-Ross.
班
Ben.
班…
I mean,Ben. Ben.
雷蒙，乔伊，该你们上场了
Raymond,Joey,you're up.
好，现在要…
So here's what....
我一定有在哪里见过你
Are you sure that I haven't seen you somewhere before?
没有，我从没演过戏
No,I haven't been in any plays.
好吧，我们来试一次
All right,let's try one.
你们准备好了就开始
Whenever you guys are ready.
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?
这是面汤 我练习时是用番茄汤
Well,this is noodle soup. And I've been working with tomato.
不过没关系…
But that's okay. No problem.
面汤…
Mmm...noodle soup.
你那样不错 不过台词是“汤”
You know,that's fine. But the line is,"Mmm...soup."
那我刚才说什么？
-What'd I say?
“面汤”
-"Mmm...noodle soup."
有什么不一样？
How's that different?
对…
Yes
好，我们来试一次
All right. Let's try one.
面汤
Mmm...noodle soup.
好，我们再来一次 好
Let's do it again.
汤，我是说“面汤” 不对，是“汤”
Mmm...soup.I mean,noodle soup. I mean,soup!
拜托
Come on!
我们得换下一组了
You know what? We need to move on.
不…我再演一次，你看
No,I could do it one more time.Look.
面汤…可恶！
Mmm...noodle soup.Damn it!
周一前把样品交给杂志社 应该就没问题了
So I think that if we get these samples into the magazine by Monday,we'll be fine.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
瑞秋，你还好吗？ 好极了
So,Rach,how you doing?-I'm great!
不，我是说戒烟的事
-No,with the not-smoking thing.
我快要死了，跟你说
Kill me now.Let me tell you something,
我今天吃了40个棉花糖
I ate 40 Mallomars today.
全身贴满了戒烟贴布
I mean,I have patches all over my body,you know?
我连续两天都失眠
-I mean,I haven't slept in two days.
我们昨天才戒烟的
-We quit yesterday.
我连今天都算进去了
That's counting today.
言归正传，我想这些样品…
But anyway,so these samples,I think
天啊，我忘记了，真的很抱歉 我得去收发室寄送样张
Oh,my God!I'm so sorry,I forgot. I have to go to the mailroom and mail some proofs.
去吧 我和瑞秋继续来脑力激荡
Go ahead. Rachel and I will just sit here and keep brainstorming.
时尚杂志也想知道… 你知道吗？…
Also,Vogue called. And they were wondering
我有点饿了 我要去贩卖机买东西
You know what? I'm a little hungry. I'm just gonna run down to the vending machines.
好吧
All right.
被逮到了
Busted!
你们这是在干嘛？ 我们不是戒烟姐妹花吗？
Come on! What are you doing? I thought we were the Patch Sisters.
对，那样行不通
That didn't work out.
那我们说过的那些事呢？
Wait a minute. What about all we've talked about?
说这恶心的地方，丑陋的人
You know,the disgusting place,the ugly people.
你好吗？
Hey,how you doing?
瑞秋，我们有试着戒烟 但那实在是太难了
We tried to quit. But it was too hard.
你们开始抽烟 起码也该告诉我嘛
If you started smoking again,you could have at least told me.
快点来一支，刚才说到哪里？
Give me one. What are we talking about?
不行，你戒烟很成功 不许放弃
Don't you give up.
所以我们才没跟你说 我们不想拖你下水
That's why we didn't tell you,and we won't drag you down.
等等，别这样，拖我下水…
Wait. No,no. Drag me down.
瑞秋，万万不可 你戒烟成功，我们都替你骄傲
Forget it. We're so proud of how well you're doing.
我不能让你前功尽弃
I won't let you blow it.
若被我查到你有吸烟 我一定炒你鱿鱼
If I catch you,you're fired.
走吧，离开这里 我不要你吸二手烟
Go on,get out of here. I don't want you breathing this stuff.
好，你和我一起去法国出差
So,okay. You'll come with me on the Paris trip?
要命！
Oh,man!
你瞧瞧，杯子帽
Check it out. Cup hat,
杯子布条
cup banner...
杯子吊灯
...cup chandelier,
还有这些东西的起源：杯子
and the thing that started it all: the cup!
菲比，你对杯子还真有一套
Great job with the cups.
你干脆跟她去约会算了
Why don't you just go out with her?
你有没有注意到冰？
Did you notice the ice? Look!
各式各样的都有
We have it all.
有碎冰、冰块…
We have crushed,cubed
还有干冰，注意看
and dry. Watch.
很有神秘感吧？
Mystical.
没人想吃我的小点心 他们全跑去吃菲比的雪花冰
No one's eating my food. They're eating her snow cones!
有雪花冰？
There are snow cones?
雪花冰最恶心了！
Snow cones！Yuck
你去吃啦 谢谢…
-Go,go! -Thank you.
菲比？
Phoebe
你做的很棒
-You really did do a nice job.
谢谢你，很明显
-Thank you...for stating the obvious.
我活该
I deserve that.
我只是要让你知道
I just want you to know that...
若我们下回再一起主办派对 你想要怎么做都行
if we ever cohost a party together again...you can do whatever you want.
乔伊的生日快到了 真的？
-Joey's got a birthday coming up.-Really?
那你要怎么帮他庆祝？
What do you wanna do?
好，我想要负责啤酒
-Okay,I'd like to be in charge of beer.
那我就没的做了
Well,then there's nothing left for me.
注意！…
-Look,look!
惊喜！
-Surprise!
什么啊？ 一个月后才是我生日啊
What? My birthday is not for another month.
这样才惊喜啊
That's the surprise.
天啊，你们太棒了
Oh,my God,you guys! This is so great!
我完全没想到 我的意思是钱德的生日比我还要早的
It's so unexpected.I mean,Chandler's birthday is even before mine.
惊喜！
Surprise!
真是太棒了，看看这些杯子
This is so great! Look at all these...cups.
真是怪怪的
...This is so weird
杯子是我负责的
I was in charge of cups.
好，那就没那么怪了
Oh,okay. Not so weird.
钱德，你在干嘛？ 没干嘛
-Chandler,what are you doing? -Nothing.
你手里拿的是什么？ 钱，我偷走了所有的钱
-What's in your hand? -Money. I'm stealing all the money.
钱德
Chandler.
抽一支就好 因为没有人记得我的生日
But just one,okay? Because nobody knows when my birthday is.
或许这能让你清醒一点
Let me make this clear to you,okay?
有香烟…
It's either that...
就没有我
...or this.
刚才那是薄荷烟
They were menthol.
我很遗憾你试镜不顺利
Listen,man. I'm sorry the audition didn't go well.
是喔
Yeah,right.
乔伊，我是真的很遗憾
No,really. I am,Joey. I feel bad.
罗斯，你用不着遗憾
Look,Ross. You don't have to,okay?
是我自己逊，怨不得你
It's not your fault I suck.
连“面汤”都说不好 还算哪门子的演员？
What kind of an actor can't even say,"Mmm...noodle soup"?
你知道吗？或许你搞砸了试镜 不是因为你逊
You know what? Maybe you didn't mess up your audition because you suck.
或许你搞砸了试镜 是因为你更在意你的教子
Maybe you messed up because you care more about your godson.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我认为，在潜意识里…
I think,subconsciously
等等，我听不懂
You lost me.
我觉得在某种程度上
I think,on some level,
你破坏了自己的试镜
you sabotaged...your own audition
才好让班拿到那个角色
...so Ben would get the part.
你的说法比我的好多了
Your way sounds a lot better than mine.
对，不是我演技烂 对
It's not that I'm a bad actor.
只是我太顾念班了
No,it's just that I care so damn much about little Ben...
看到他成功对我来说更重要
...that it was more important for me to see him succeed.
就是这样，谢谢你 谢谢你
-There you go. Thank you. -Thank you.
那他拿到角色没？ 没有
-So did he get it? -No.
那没办法了
What are you gonna do?
不好意思，瑞秋格林在吗？ 我跟她约了吃中饭
Is Rachel Green here? I'm meeting her for lunch.
她现在不会下来这里了 她在十楼
She doesn't come down anymore. You'll find her on 10.
好…
Okay,great.
我们昨天中饭聊到提案报告 他担心一个人不太够
So we talked about the presentation.He wondered if one person would be enough.
我说绝对没问题
And I said,"Yeah,absolutely."
待会见
I'll catch you guys later.